康纳堡
弗吉尼亚州美军基地
储藏室
军用单兵口粮
快点  它们醒了
快
Come on.
行尸走肉
第十一季  第一集
欢迎来到亚历山大
过来  小子
Come on, boy!
妈妈  妈妈
Mom! Mom!
科尔有个惊喜
Cole has a surprise!
猜猜谁来了
Guess who this cat dragged in.
阿加莎
Agatha!
没那么容易甩掉我们的  孩子
Can't get rid of us that easy, kid.
骑大马
Shoulders.
我也想你  小子
I missed you, too, man.
很高兴见到你  小玛
It's good to see you, Mags.
我也是  邓肯
Good to see you, too, Duncan.
我还以为你们死了
I thought you guys were dead.
我们也以为你死了
We thought the same about you.
我们到了子午镇  结果
When we got to Meridian, we, uh...
我们想着如果你还活着  就会来这里
well, we figured if you were still alive, you'd be here.
那是他吗
That him?
是给我家人的
For my family, man!
别打了
Hey, break it up.
-拜托  那是我的  好吗  -我说了别打了
- Come on. That's mine, alright? - I said break it up.
拜托
Come on.
大家都冷静点
Everyone calm down.
每个人都能分到食物
There's enough food for everyone.
一周
One week.
就这么久  上次我们搜来的东西就够一周吗
That's it? In that last run, just a week?
我们能撑过去的
We can make it work.
怎么撑
How?
我们刚收留了两个新社区的人
We just took in two new communities.
我们没有庄稼和存粮
We have no crops, no back stock.
我们会有办法的
We can get there.
现在就有人在外面忙碌
Got people out there right now,
搜索房子  寻找物资
scavenging houses for materials.
他们慢下来了
And they're slowing down.
用损坏的工具建一堵墙
It's a little hard to put up a wall
同时还饥肠辘辘  这有点难
with broken tools and an empty stomach.
我们的人擅长打猎
Our people are good hunters.
弗罗斯特和我可以带一队人出去
Frost and I could take a group out.
这片地区没猎物了
Ground's all spent.
上一批大尸群把所有的动物都吓跑了
The last big horde scared all the animals away.
我们可以去找新猎场
We can find new territory.
我们没时间  我们需要食物
We don't have time. We need food.
大量食物  现在就要
Lots of it. Now.
我还知道一个地方
I know one more place.
之前我住在那
The place I lived before this.
我们都住在那
Where we lived.
子午镇
Meridian.
那里有大量的食物  水  庄稼和动物
It's got plenty of food, water, crops, and animals.
是啊  但现在陷落了
Yeah, and now it's gone.
那里发生了什么
So, what happened out there?
我们当时在执行一项任务
We were on a mission.
引开行尸
Leading walkers away.
邓肯  阿加莎和弗罗斯特
Duncan, Agatha, and Frost
引开了最后一批行尸
took the last shift at the front of the herd.
走了几英里
Going miles out.
我和伊莱哲还有科尔绕了回去
I circled back with Elijah, Cole.
回家的路上  事情一直不顺
On the way back home, things kept going sideways
我们被困在了路上
and we got stuck out on the road.
现在回想起来  我觉得那不是意外
Looking back now, I don't think that was an accident.
突然  我们听到远方传来了尖叫声
All of a sudden, we heard these screams in the distance.
我们跑回家
We raced back home.
但是太迟了
But it was too late.
我们的大部分人都被杀了
Most of our people had been slaughtered.
剩下的人侥幸逃过一劫
And the rest of us barely got away with our lives.
关于攻击我们的人
The people that attacked us --
我们只知道两点
we only knew two things about them.
他们晚上行动
They come at night,
等你看到他们  你就已经是死人了
and by the time you see them, you're already dead.
在那之后  我们抓到了一个人
That was before we caught one.
达里尔当时跟我在一起
Daryl was with me.
他一个人来追杀我们
He came after us alone.
为什么
Why?
因为他们人不多
Because there aren't that many of them.
他们现在在子午镇
They're at Meridian now.
那里有足够的食物养活亚历山大人
There's plenty of food to feed Alexandria
直到我们恢复这里的秩序
'til we get this place back up and running again.
所以他们才夺走了子午镇
That's why they took it.
我们只用夺回来
We just need to take it back.
你要去跟鬼打仗
So...you're leaving to fight ghosts.
这就是你的计划吗
That's the plan?
你有更好的计划吗
You have a better one?
首先  加固亚历山大的防线
Shore up Alexandria, for starters.
墙并不牢固
The walls are not stable.
行尸会进来的
Walkers will get inside.
那只是时间问题
That's not if, it's when.
亚历山大需要我们
Alexandria needs us.
这就是为了亚历山大
This is for Alexandria.
我的儿子在这里
My son is here.
这也与我息息相关
I have skin in the game, too.
但如果他们能一下杀了所有人
Yeah, but if they slaughtered everyone once,
这次的情况又有什么不同呢
what the hell makes this situation any different?
邓肯  阿加莎和弗罗斯特是子午镇最强的战士
Duncan, Agatha, and Frost are Meridian's best fighters,
现在他们与我并肩作战
and now I have them.
希望你们中的某些人也会加入
And hopefully, some of you, too.
玛姬  这听起来像是自杀任务
Maggie, this sounds like a suicide mission.
如果我们没有食物
Well, if we don't have food,
反正我们也会死
it's not gonna matter, anyway.
我愿意去
I'll go.
还有人吗
Anybody else?
行
Alright.
尼根  我们还要多久才能穿过这座城市
Negan, how much longer 'til we're through the city?!
大概六个小时
Well, we got about six hours!
我们该找地躲雨  等雨停了再走
We should hunker down, wait for this to pass!
轮不到你决定  混蛋
You don't get a vote, asshole!
他说得对  我们得找个躲雨的地方
Ah, he's right. We need to find some shelter.
不  我们没时间
No! We don't have time!
我们不能在暴雨里待着
We can't stay out in this.
地铁
行  去吧
Yeah. Let's go.
地铁派隆
凉荫丛站
美国不容忍种族主义
好  走哪边
Alright. Which way?
我不想一直喋喋不休
Not to sound like a broken record,
但我们应该喘口气
but I think we ought to take a breath,
休息会  等这场暴雨过去
hunker down, and wait for this storm to pass.
你不想进去吗
You don't wanna go in there?
我不想
No, I don't.
我不在乎
I don't give a shit.
走哪条路
Which way?
沿黄线向北走
Yellow line north.
在里根国家机场换蓝线
Switch to blue at Reagan National,
然后走红线到贝塞斯达
then hop the red toward Bethesda.
我们走吧
Come on. Let's go.
我能和你谈谈吗
Hey, can I talk to you?
为什么
Why's that?
你觉得我们是好哥们吗
You think we're buddies or something?
走吧
Come on.
走吧  狗
Come on, boy.
如果有上帝  他得求我宽恕
那是什么声音
What the hell was that?
暴雨将空气压入管道
The storm's pushing air through the pipes,
发出了吱嘎声
making them groan.
不严重  没事的
It's nothing serious. We're good.
知道那其实是什么声音吗
Know what that noise actually is?
上帝叫我们掉头的声音
That is God, telling us to turn around.
我敢肯定他会先跟我说的
I'm pretty sure He would have ran that by me first.
是吗  上帝让你的独眼看到这个了吗
Yeah? The Good Lord direct your one eyeball to this?
水线
Water-line mark.
意味着这条隧道经常被洪水淹没
That means this tunnel floods on a regular basis,
比如下雨时
like when it rains.
下面很糟糕  但上面更惨
It's bad down here. It's worse up there.
听着  我只是说
Look, man, all I am saying --
那没用
And it ain't working.
你想管事
You trying to run shit.
继续走
Keep moving.
走吧
Come on.
狗
Dog!
你也有份
You're in on it.
尤金·伯特
Eugene Porter?
是
Yes.
那是我的教名
That is my given moniker, yes.
你不必紧张  伯特先生
There's no need to be nervous, Mr. Porter.
只要你说实话
Not if you're honest with us.
认识我的人都知道我是一位可敬的绅士
Those who know me, know me to be an honorable gent.
如果你指的是我的谈吐
If you're inferring something from my manner of speaking, well...
那只是我的风格
that's just how I roll.
我是指言语上
Verbally, that is.
我们是联邦的审查员
We are Auditors for the Commonwealth,
你正处于一级评估中
and you are under Level One Assessment.
如果你通过了检查  就会升到二级
If you pass inspection, you'll move to Level Two.
如果我们通不过检查呢
What if we don't pass inspection?
那就要进行重新评估
You will go through re-processing.
什么是重新评估
What's re-processing?
现在开始评估吧
We should start the assessment.
你的父母以前是做什么工作的
What did your parents do for a living?
我父亲是一名机械工程师  然后
My father was a mechanical engineer, and --
我妈妈是主日学校老师
My mother taught Sunday school.
你是指无良废柴一号
You mean deadbeat loser number one
还是易怒混蛋二号
or raging prick number two?
你以前是做什么工作的
What did you do for a living?
我是动物园管理员
I was a zookeeper.
我在一家音像店上班
I worked at a music store.
-我是个律师  -你的母校是哪里
- Lawyer. - What is your alma mater?
-这有什么关系  -只是流程需要  女士
- What's the relevance? - It's just procedure, ma'am.
我在牛津取得了学士学位
I attended Oxford for my bachelor's,
在哈佛学了法律
Harvard for Law.
最高学历
Highest level of schooling?
在北卡罗来纳大学读了三年
Three years at the University of North Carolina.
你没有毕业吗
You didn't graduate?
-我离开是因为...  -那就是没有了
- I had to leave due to a... - So, no?
你的邮政区号是多少
What was your zip code?
谁会记得那种事
How can anyone possibly be expected to remember that?
从1978年到1984年是75001
From 1978 to 1984, it was 75001.
从1984到1996是76244-0361
From 1984 to 1996, it was 76244-0361.
1996年下半年到...
From latter half of 1996 through --
你的上一次常规体检是什么结果
What were the results of your last routine physical?
我没做过体检
Uh...I-I don't think I've had one.
你接种过麻疹疫苗吗
Have you ever been vaccinated for measles?
你需要知道详细日期吗
Would you like the dates?
有癌症病史吗
Any history of cancer?
没有
None.
你的甲状腺肿是怎么回事
Tell me about the goiter.
这是良性瘤
It's a benign growth.
我从小就有
I've had it since childhood.
我们在你身上发现的现金是哪里来的
Where did you get the cash we found on you?
那张两元吗
The $2 bill?
告诉我们是从哪里来的
Tell us exactly where you got it.
我15岁的时候
Uh, so, when I was 15,
第一份工作是在米西·穆斯比萨店
my first job was at Missy Moose's Pizzeria.
-就是那个...  -直接讲重点
- You know, the... - You can skip to the end.
我去银行兑薪水时
When I cashed my paycheck at the bank,
要了一张两元钞票  专门保存了起来
I asked for a $2 bill so I could keep it,
因为这是我自己挣的第一笔钱
because it was the first money I'd ever earned.
等我们回答完问题后
When we're done with these questions,
能把那两元还我吗
can I get my $2 back?
你被逮捕过吗
Have you ever been arrested?
-没有  -没有
- No. - No.
-有  但不是我干的  -有  学生抗议的时候
- Yeah, but it wasn't me. Wasn't me. - Yes, during a student protest.
-药物[毒品]史呢  -"药物"指什么
- History of drug use? - Define "Drug".
我在高中时期
I was a proud founding member
是反药酒联盟的荣誉创始成员
of the anti-drug and alcohol coalition at my high school.
你一天排便多少次
How many bowel movements do you have a day?
什么
Excuse me?
-你用什么擦屁股  -不想说
- What do you use to wipe? - Pass.
你为什么会在那个火车站
Why were you at the train station?
我和我的旅伴一起在旅行
I was on the road with my traveling companions,
以西结和由美子
Ezekiel and Yumiko --
...好几年来  到处流浪
...for years, wandering from place to place.
我们遇到了公主
We ran into Princess --
...我帮助了他们  他们爱我
...I helped them out. They loved me.
我就决定跟着他们了
I decided to stick with 'em.
我们藏身在一个能用无线电的地方
We were holed up at a place that had a working radio.
我和史蒂芬妮联系上了
Stephanie and I made a connection.
我们想要见面  但我的朋友们都很担心  所以我
We wanted to meet, but my friends were worried, so I --
假装我们还有更多人
...pretended like there were more of us than there really are.
所以我们才会出现在那个站台
And that's how we wound up at the rail yard.
So we wound up at the rail yard.
我很想和史蒂芬妮聊聊
I would really like to speak with Stephanie.
你认为你算是一个诚实的人吗
Do you consider yourself a fundamentally honest person?
-是的  -当然了
- Yes. - Of course.
-是的  -那当然
- Yes. - Hell yeah.
你母亲会出门工作吗
Did your mother work outside the home?
我和你说过了  基督教浸信会恩惠堂
I told you. Grace Baptist Church.
你们的聚居地在哪里
What's the location of your settlement?
你已经问过这个问题了
You already asked that one.
你的最高学历是什么
What was your highest level of education attainment?
-你们聚居地的地点  -什么聚居地
- Location of your settlement? - What settlement?
你们遇到过其他团体吗
Have you run into any groups out there?
我们遇到过一些不友善的人
We've had some negative encounters.
你幸运吗  为什么
How lucky are you and why?
什么
What?
你们聚居地的地点
Location of your settlement.
你觉得这很好笑吗
Do you think this is funny?
是的
Yeah.
我是这么觉得
Yeah, I do.
你是管事的吗
Are you in charge?
你一直站在那里  一言不发
You've been standing there, not saying a damn word
感觉像是管事的
like you're the man in charge.
对
Yeah.
我是管事的
I'm in charge.
你觉得我怕你吗
Do you think that I fear you?
在我看来你挺怕的
You look scared to me.
你在灾变之前是做什么的
What did you do before the fall?
我猜猜  是个混蛋片警吧
Let me guess. Asshole beat cop.
所以才对这套法西斯做法如此驾轻就熟
That's why this fascist crap comes so easy to you.
瞧瞧你
Look at you.
他们只需要给你一套
All they had to do was give you
南瓜色的太空服
a pumpkin-colored space suit
你就又开始滥用权势了
and you're back to power tripping
趾高气扬的  和从前一样
with your head up your own ass, just like before.
你觉得我是那种"滥用职权的警察"
You think I was some "power tripping cop"?
看着像  但说实话  我不在乎
The shoe fits. But honestly, I don't care.
你们一直在问我们同样的问题
You've been asking us the same damn questions
一遍又一遍  整整七个小时
over and over for seven hours straight.
我一直很配合
I've been cooperative.
我的同伴也很配合
My people have been cooperati--
口渴吗
Thirsty?
我没事
I'm fine.
你居然训斥了他们的头儿
You told off their leader?
我是在树立威信
I was asserting myself.
也许我是可以应付得更好一些  但...
Perhaps I could've handled it better, but...
我不喜欢他们和我说话的方式
I didn't like the way they talked to me.
-以西结  他们知不知道...  -他们不知道
- Ezekiel, do they know -- - No. They don't know.
没事的
Gonna be fine.
他们似乎很关注我们的病史
They seem obsessed with our medical histories.
-他们也许不会让你...  -我说了别担心
- They might not let you -- - I said don't worry about it.
我们得逃离这里
We gotta pull the rip cord on this.
是的
Yes.
是的  谢谢
Yes. Thank you.
这地方...
This place is...
我甚至不知道这到底是什么地方
I don't even know what this place is.
有没有人觉得这个联邦甚至可能不是真的
And does anyone else think the Commonwealth might not be real?
没错  由美子  谢谢
Yes, Yumiko. Thank you.
我还以为你不这么认为呢  但是...
I assumed you would think otherwise, but --
没关系  不重要了  该逃了  我们得...
It doesn't matter. Never mind. Time to get out. We gotta --
不不不
No, no, no, no.
拜托了  别急着下决定
Please, hold -- hold onto your horses.
他们确实在问一些奇怪又烦人的问题
Look, they're asking admittedly strange and intrusive questions,
但问得挺有礼貌的
but in a polite manner,
这个粥也不是我吃过最差的食物
and this gruel is not the worst thing I've ever eaten.
史蒂芬妮提醒过我她的同伴都很谨慎
Stephanie warned me up front that her people were uber-cautious.
米琼恩  我们的米琼恩
Michonne -- our Michonne --
好几年都不收留其他人进入亚历山大
shut people out from Alexandria for years.
这是个测试
This is a test.
我们应该静观其变  争取升级
We have to hunker down and level up.
也许我们该对那位"赤焰战警"说实话
Maybe we should just get honest with the "heat".
-不  -你指那些大兵警察吗
- No. - Oh, you mean the solider-cops?
你真的希望这群人带着机枪利刃
You really want these guys rolling up to Hilltop
前往山顶寨或是亚历山大吗
or Alexandria with their machine-gun swords?
我错了
Apologies.
我们的人需要帮助
Our people need help, and I-
而我觉得这些人能帮到我们
I think these people can give it.
抱歉
Excuse me?
打扰一下
Uh, sorry to bother,
能不能告诉我  你们在这里待了多久
but you mind me asking how long you've been here?
-四个月  -九个月
- Four -- Four months. - Nine.
已经九个月了  记得吗
It's been nine, remember?
对哦  没错  那个重新评估...
Right. Yeah. The -- The re-processing...
但感觉终于要...
But -- But it feels like things are finally --
抱歉  什么意思
I'm sorry. What do you mean?
等等  等等
Wait. Wait!
等等  不要
Wait, no! No!
住手  住手
Stop! Stop!
等等  我做错什么了
Wait! Wait! What did I do?
你们要带我去哪里
Where are you taking me?
重新评估
Re-processing.
好吧  我们得逃
Okay, we gotta go.
为什么它没出一点声
Why didn't it make any noise?
喉咙伤口过深  头都快掉了
Throat's slashed so deep it almost severed his head.
是我们在找的那群人干的吗
The guys we're going after do this?
不是
No.
这些人是灾变时被杀的
These people were killed during the fall.
全部都是吗
All of 'em?
什么
What?
我们正在穿越一个可能仍在被使用的乱葬岗
We're walking through a mass grave that could still be in use.
所以我想问
So, I am asking you --
你确定他们所有人都是灾变时被杀的吗
are you sure all of them were killed during the fall?
全部干掉
Take each one out.
清出道路
Clear the path.
-玛姬  等等...  -我们不能停
- Maggie, hold up --- We're not stopping.
孩子
Kid!
密切注意  别再有遗漏
Pay attention so we don't miss any more.
密切注意
Pay attention?
就这样吗
That's it? That's --
这就是你的伟大新计划
That's your new big plan?
告诉我  玛姬  有什么
Tell me, Maggie, anything in particular
是我们需要特别注意的吗
we should be paying attention to?
我快忍不住想堵上你的嘴了
I'm real close to shoving a gag in your mouth.
那你踮脚试试看够不够得着
Well, why don't you get up on your little tippy toes and try?
你俩都别吵了
Cut it out. Both of you.
这孩子差点死了
This kid almost died.
你根本不在乎那孩子
You don't give a shit about that kid.
不  是她不在乎
No, she doesn't give a shit.
我们离开后她一直在扮演独裁者
She has been playing dictator since we left,
不听我的  不听他的
not listening to me, not listening to him.
连你的话也不听
Hell, not even listening to you.
我们不知道这隧道到底有没有出口
We don't know if this tunnel even has a way out.
不管是什么人或东西杀了那些腐尸
Whoever or whatever killed these rot bags
他们都有可能还在这里
could still be down here.
你们有人想过吗
Has that thought crossed anyone's mind?
没错  有想过
Exactly. It has.
那这就是一趟死亡之旅
So, then this is a death march,
而你是该死的领头笛手
and you are the goddamn pied piper.
你们想顺着她  没关系
Now, y'all wanna roll with that shit, that's fine.
随便你们
Knock yourselves out.
但我不会  今天不会
But not me. Not today.
我退出
I am out.
我也是
Me, too.
什么
What?
他是个混蛋  但他说得有道理
He-- He's a dick, but he makes sense.
没错  我们就不该下来
Yeah, we shouldn't have come down here.
我们不能分开
We're not splitting up.
这由不得你决定  "好哥们"
It ain't up to you. "Buddy".
让他走吧
Just let him go.
他本该帮我们的
He's supposed to be helping us,
但他只是在拖慢我们
but all he's doing is slowing us down.
-不行  -为什么
- Can't. - Why not?
我们需要他  他熟悉这城市
We need him. He knows the city.
这是我来这的原因吗
Oh, is that why I'm here?
我是你的华盛顿导游
I-I'm your DC tour guide?
怎么  这里没人会看他妈的地图吗
What, nobody here know how to read a goddamn map?
我告诉你我为什么在这  男人婆
I'll tell you why I'm here, man-tits.
她带我来这送死
She brought me here to die.
就算我们能熬过这段  我也回不去了
If we get through this, I'm not coming back.
她会想个办法  找个理由
She'll find a way, she'll find a reason,
她会亲自动手
she'll do it herself.
远离亚历山大的监管视线
Away from the prying eyes of Alexandria.
在这丛林里
Here in the jungle.
我本来以为你也有份
Man, I really thought you were in on it.
真的
I did.
但我从你茫然的眼神中能看出
But see, I can tell from that glazed look in your eyes,
你毫不知情
you didn't have a clue.
你们都不知情
None of you did.
你太多疑了
You're paranoid.
但我是对的
But I'm right.
你们都想把命交到她手里吗
Look, you all want to put your lives in her hands?
可她压根没专心投入
Her head isn't even in the game
因为我就住在她大脑里  还免租
because I'm in her head, living rent-free.
所以玛姬  我按你的想法死
So, Maggie, me dying on your terms,
这绝对不可能
it ain't happening.
你怎么说
So, what do you say?
直接动手吧
Let's just get her done.
在此时此处
Right here and right now.
因为我不会任由你拖着我趟过泥巴
Because I am not gonna let you drag me through the mud,
污秽和黏液  然后把我像条狗一样杀了
filth, and slime to put me down like a dog.
就像格伦一样
Like Glenn was.
我们下来是因为上面是死路一条
We're down here because up top is death.
我们快速行进是因为我们的孩子在挨饿
We're moving fast because our kids are starving.
我发号施令是因为这是所有人投票的结果
And I'm calling the shots because that's how everyone voted.
至于我要杀了你
As for me killing you...
这念头一直在我脑海里
It's always on my mind.
我不会告诉你你看错我了
I'm not gonna tell you that you're wrong about me,
因为你没看错
because you aren't.
现在站在你眼前的女人
The woman who left six years ago
已经不是六年前离开的那个女人了
is not the one standing over you now.
我内心还残留着一小部分的她
There's a little bit of her left in me,
就是那一部分保住了你的性命
and that little bit is the only thing keeping you breathing.
但我不知道能持续多久
But I don't know how long that's gonna last.
所以继续逼我  尼根
So keep pushing me, Negan.
求你了
Please.
你有什么想法  公主
What do you think, Princess?
公主
Princess.
抱歉  什么
I'm sorry, what?
有想法吗  如何躲过守卫
Ideas? How to get past the guards.
还没有
Oh, yeah. Not yet.
什么  你在看什么
What? What are you looking at?
利维茨和泽尔又开始了
Livits and Zell are at it again.
谁和谁怎么了
What and who-who?
总是在调情的那俩人
You know, the two that are always flirting with each other.
大块头利维茨
The big guy -- Livits.
小瘦子泽尔
The skinny one -- Zell.
你知道他们的名字
You know their names?
-嗯  -你能分清他们
- Yeah. - You can tell them apart?
-你分不清吗  -好吧  这是浪费时间
- You can't? - Okay, we're wasting time.
等等  公主  你是怎么分清他们的
Hold on. Princess, how can you tell them apart,
你为什么认为他俩在调情
and -- and why do you believe that those two are flirting?
怎么说呢
Oh, I dunno.
我在马车上无意中听到了他们的对话
I overheard stuff when were on the wagon,
我对别人的事记得特熟
and I remember things about people, you know?
比如  泽尔来自克利夫兰
Like, Zell is from Cleveland.
利维茨的腿受过伤  所以他左腿走路轻
Livits hurt his leg, so he favors the left one.
索伦森抽烟  他不喜欢加西亚
Sorsensen smokes. He doesn't like Garcia.
就是那个尿频的人
That's the guy with the bladder problems.
在来这里的路上  我总是问他
I always used to ask him if I needed a pee break
需不需要去撒尿
when we were driving here.
利维茨和泽尔在做爱
Oh, and Livits and Zell are having sex,
但他们不想让任何人知道
but they don't want anyone to know.
他们没看彼此啊
They're not looking at each other.
对  但他们
Yeah, but it's obvious
不看彼此的方式太明显了
from the way they're not looking at each other
仿佛欲火难耐
that they're jonesing for it.
他们每六小时换一次班
They, uh, change shifts every six hours.
每次休息时  他们中一人会先走
Whenever they're on break, one of them takes off,
三分钟后  另一个人也会走
and then three minutes later, the other one disappears, too.
消失差不多一个小时
Gone for about an hour, mas o menos.
大部分时间估计都花在脱盔甲上了
Probably most of the time is spent taking off their armor.
你上次常规体检是什么结果
What was the result of your last routine physical?
我不明白这些问题
I don't understand these questions!
你到底在说什么
What are you talking about?
你们要带他俩去哪里
Where are you taking those two?
对啊  我也想知道
Yeah, that's what I'd like to know!
太过分了  我们有权利的
This is bullshit! We have rights!
重新评估
Re-processing.
去吧
Move along.
没收以焚毁
加快审核并纳入联邦
失踪者之墙
A wall of the lost.
我们能直接去后门
We have a straight shot to the back gate,
但必须现在走
but we gotta go now.
由美子
Yumiko!
-快走  -不
- Let's go, let's go! - No.
看
Mira.
这不是你吗
Isn't that you?
如果你见过
我的姐妹由美子
请联系托米
由美子
Yumiko!
我
I...
我必须留下
I have to stay.
糟了
Shit.
得换电池了
Need a battery swap.
盖奇
Gage?
盖奇  罗伊
Gage? Roy?
有人看到他们了吗
Has anyone seen them?
他们拿走了补给
They took our supplies.
弹药  口粮
Ammo clips, rations --
真好  真是太好了
Oh, great. That's just great.
都怪这个混球  他吓跑了他们
It's this asshole's fault. He scared them off.
听
Listen.
好  拦住它们
Alright. Cut them off.
-我们干掉剩下的  -阿加莎
- We'll clear the rest. - Agatha!
-堵住了  -这边也是
- Blocked. - Here, too.
拿着  我试试
Hold this. Let me try.
退后  快
Fall back! Now!
快走
Go! Go!
-让开  -能绕过去吗
- Go! - Can we get around it?
堵住了  我们不知道另一边有什么
It's a choke point. We don't know what's on the other side.
上面
Up top.
去上面
Go, all the way up.
上去  爬到车厢上面
Go, man. Up top. On top of the car.
去  快点
Go. Hurry.
上去
Come on, man, get up.
爬上去  快
All the way up to the top. Go!
过来  小子
Come here, boy.
狗  不  过来  狗
Dog! No! Come here! Dog!
快走
Go. Let's go. Let's go.
在下一站等我
Meet me at the next platform.
-达里尔  等等  -我会没事的  走吧
- Daryl, wait. - I'll be fine. Go.
-达里尔  等等  -狗
- Daryl, wait! - Dog!
狗  狗
Dog! Dog!
尼根
Negan!